{
    "id": "812f6bd14a7946b18fab58ac8b5ec33b",
    "title": "If And Unless Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I cannot go …………………. he gives me permission.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "unless"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a2b9f75294934faa96511de4bc3075ab"
        },
        {
            "question": "We cannot live …………………. we do not eat.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "unless"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1e0c9dd38f9c4477aec48f8831acc744"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… the rain stops, we will go out.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "Unless"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a4c83cf5c122414984dd16df2271482d"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………… I had enough money, I would buy a car.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "Unless"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ab0f9d346f064344b8a46feea2d7722a"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………….. he expresses regret, he will not be allowed to enter the class.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Unless",
                "If"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d21e148499e94fedb8cba214cc092956"
        },
        {
            "question": "He would be very happy ………………….. you invited him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "unless"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b5113d61bcee4bbcbc22a97c83623c62"
        },
        {
            "question": "You won’t get better ………………… you stop smoking.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "unless"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "148cd56d18894854980e3d6e8f7e968f"
        },
        {
            "question": "He will become the chief minister …………………. his party wins majority.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "unless"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7058f32303bd4434a31df55091f26a76"
        },
        {
            "question": "You will fall ill ………………….. you expose yourself to the cold wind.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "unless"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2fef00fb8dec41b6866c9120e276d34c"
        },
        {
            "question": "He won’t be promoted …………………… he wins the confidence of his manager.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "unless"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6e67738a69fb41049665439013090d3a"
        }
    ]
}